The Perfect Fan
完美粉丝
It takes a lot to know what is love
需要经历很多，才能明白什么是爱
It's not the big things
不是什么大事
But the little things that can mean enough
而是些细碎小事，就足以证明爱
A lot of prayers to get me through
很多次的祈祷帮我渡过了难关
And there is never a day that passes by
过去的日子里没有一天
I don't think of you
我不在想念你
You were always there for me
你总是陪伴在我身边
Pushing me and guiding me
鞭策我，指引我
Always to succeed
直到我成功为止
You showed me
你教会了我
When I was young just how to grow
当年轻时，我该如何成长
You showed me
你教会了我
Everything that I should know
我应该知晓的每一件事
You showed me
你教会了我
Just how to walk without your hands
离开你时我该怎样前进
'Cause mom you always were the perfect fan
因为妈妈你一直都是——我的完美粉丝
God has been so good
上帝如此慷慨
Blessing me with a family who did all they could
赐予我一个愿意为我付出一切的家庭
And I've had many years of grace
我享受了多年的恩宠
And it flatters me when I see a smile on your face
你脸上的笑容也让我感到高兴
I wanna thank you for what you've done
我要感谢你所做的一切
In hopes I can give back to you
希望我可以好好报答你
And be the perfect son
做一个优秀的儿子
You showed me
你教会了我
When I was young just how to grow
当年轻时，我该如何成长
You showed me
你教会了我
Everything that I should know
我应该知晓的每一件事
You showed me
你教会了我
Just how to walk without your hands
离开你时我该怎样前进
'Cause mom you always were the perfect fan
因为妈妈你一直都是——我的完美粉丝
You showed me how to love
你教会我如何去爱
You showed me how to care
你教会我如何关怀
And you showed me that you would always be there
你教会了我，你会一直在那里守护我
I wanna thank you for that time
我要感谢那些你陪伴我的时光
And I'm proud to say you're mine
我可以傲娇的说，你是我的
You showed me
你教会了我
When I was young just how to grow
当年轻时，我该如何成长
You showed me
你教会了我
Everything that I should know
我应该知晓的每一件事
You showed me
你教会了我
Just how to walk without your hands
离开你时我该怎样前进
'Cause mom you always were the perfect fan
因为妈妈你一直都是——我的完美粉丝
'Cause mom you always were
因为妈妈你一直都是
Mom you always were
妈妈你一直都是
You know you always were
你知道你一直都是
'Cause mom you always were the perfect fan
因为妈妈你一直都是——我的完美粉丝
I love you mom
我爱你妈妈